# Yacine Ben Amor

#### Software engineer

A software engineer with nearly 2 years of experience looking for a rewarded career in the Information Technnology sector. Worked on a lot of projects from the concept to design, development, testing and handover. Eager to learn and able to get along with both work colleagues and senior managers. Currently looking for a suitable web developer position.



📈 benamor.yacine@yahoo.fr

Manouba, Tunisia

github.com/HolaJinn

+21620362802

in linkedin.com/in/yacine-ben-amor-46b904193

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Software Enginner**

#### Edifixio

10/2022 - Present, Tunis Clusters Configuration and workloads deployment

- Configuration of several Kubernetes clusters.
- Deployment of multiple workloads such as Keycloak and OpenLDAP to kubernetes and RedHat OpenShift clusters.
- Building Github Actions pipeline (CI/CD) to build integration applications with IBM App Connect Entreprise and deploy them to RedHat OpenShift clusters.
- Working on development, testing and maintaining of different production products using technologies such as IBM ACE, IBM APIC and IBM CP4I.

#### **Software Engineer**

#### Proxym Group

01/2022 - 06/2022, Sousse, Tunisia Design and development of a web application.

- Designed a platform which will helps to make the interviews for companies at least 75% remote.
- Detailed all the functional requirements for the application and sketched more than 30 wireframes using Balsamiq.
- Planned the general architecture of the project.
- Developed the back-end server of the application and the REST APIs using technologies such as Java, Spring Boot and PostgreSQL database.
- Coded 100% of the front-end interfaces using React with Typescript and Ant Design.
- Maintained the code on the Git branches using Github platform.
- Tested the application using Cypress and dockerizing it.

# **EDUCATION**

Computer Science Engineering
National School of Engineering of Sousse

09/2019 - 06/2022, Sousse, Tunisia

Preparatory Cycle for Engineering Studies faculty of sciences of tunis

09/2017 - 06/2019, Tunis, Tunisia

# SKILLS

HTML / CSS / Sass CSS / Sass

Node JS / Adobe XD JavaScript / TypeScript

React JS / Redux / Redux Bootstrap / Ant Design /

Toolkit Material UI

Java / Spring Boot MySQL/ PostgreSQL

Docker / Kubernetes / Git / Github Actions / Gitflow RedHat OpenShift

Cypress/JUnit IBM App Connect Entreprise

# **PERSONAL PROJECTS**

Online Image Filter (03/2020 - 06/2020)

- Made an online image filter where users can upload their images apply more than 20 filters or merge 2 images into one picture and then download it.
- Technologies: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript.

Library Management System (10/2019 - 02/2020)

- Provided a system that helps universities libraries administrations to manage all the books they have and digitalizing 80% of their system.
- Technologies: Java, Sw ing, MySQL.

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

English TOIEC Test with 815 score. (02/2022 - Present)

IBM Certified Solution Architect - Cloud Pak for Integration (02/2023 - Present)

### **LANGUAGES**

English

French

Full Professional Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

Arabic

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

# <u>INTERESTS</u>

Reading

Cinema

Gaming

Music

Technology